Guide to the 7th Regiment Records 1767-1983 (bulk, 1830-1947) MS 556
New-York Historical Society
- Series II: Companies, 1806-1949
  For other material relating to 7th Regiment companies, see rosters [c1942-1947] in the Veterans of the 7th Regiment files, Series I (Subseries 10). See also Series IX for ephemera (bulk Co. B), and Series XIV: Visual Materials for oversized items and photo albums relating to companies.
  - Box and Folder:
    - Co. A, 1826-1892 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 1)
    - Co. A: "Att-A-Boy" newsletter, 1917 Sept. 22-Oct. 16 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 2)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, A-Bi, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 3)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Bl-Bu, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 4)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Ca, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 5)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Ch-De, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 6)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Di-Fl, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 7)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Fo-Gi, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 15, Folder 8)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Gl-Ha, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 1)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, He-J, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 2)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, K, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 3)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, L, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 4)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Ma-Me, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 5)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, Mi-My, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 6)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, N-R, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 16, Folder 7)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, S, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 1)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, T-V, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 2)
    - Co. B: Enlistment Records, W-Z, 1939-1949 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 3)
    - Co. B: "Fordham & Poly Preps Recruit Applications", 1946 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 4)
    - Co. B: Information Form, Former Members, 1946 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 5)
    - [Co. B]: Correspondence--Recruitment--[G. Richard Ludlow, Capt.], 1940 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 6)
    - Co. B: Rosters, 1842, 1902-1907, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 7)
    - Co. B: Register of Members (2 copies), 1864-1910 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 8)
    - Co. B: Orders, 1835-1909 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 9)
    - Co. B: Resolutions, 1858-1892 (Offsite-box 17, Folder 10)
    - Co. B: Society of Exempt Members--Correspondence, 1890-1911 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 1)
    - Co. B: Society of Exempt Members--By-Laws, Resolutions, 1891-1896, undated (Offsite-box 18, Folder 2)
    - Co. B: Society of Exempt Members, 1900-1917 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 3)
    - Co. B: Memos, 1944, 1947 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 4)
    - Co. B: Reports, 1941 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 5)
    - Co. B: Financial Statements, 1941, 1945-1947 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 6)
    - Co. B: Circulars/Notices, 1856-1906 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 7)
    - Co. B: Photographs, [1900-1905] (Offsite-box 18, Folder 8)
    - Co. B: Returns, Misc., 1831-1945 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 9)
    - Co. C: Orders, 1852-1860 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 10)
    - Co. C: Orders, 1860-1868 (Offsite-box 18, Folder 11)
    - Co. C: Rosters, Undated (Offsite-box 19, Folder 1)
    - Co. C: Resolutions, 1851-1892 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 2)
    - Co. C: Notices, Certificates, Reports, Returns, 1826-1905 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 3)
    - [Co. D]: Orders, 1814-1825 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 4)
    - [Co. D]: Orders, 1823-1825 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 5)
    - [Co. D]: Orders, 1823-1829 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 6)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1825-1833 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 7)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1829-1841 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 8)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1858-1865 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 9)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1858-1878 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 10)
    - Co. D: Orders, 1866-1878 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 11)
    - Co. D: Resolutions, 1860-1892, 1907 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 12)
    - Co. D: Discharges, 1869 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 13)
    - Co. D: Notices, Rolls, Circulars, Constitution, 1821-1893 (Offsite-box 19, Folder 14)
    - Co. D: Photographs, 1863, [1890] (Offsite-box 19, Folder 15)
    - Co. E: Enlistment Records, A-L, 1942-1948 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 1)
    - Co. E: Enlistment Records, M-Z, 1942-1948 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 2)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1823, 1842-1851 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 3)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1859-1863 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 4)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1862-1872 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 5)
    - Co. E: Resolutions, Roll, 1852-1892 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 6)
    - Co. E: Reports, 1831, 1946 (Offsite-box 20, Folder 7)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 July-Aug. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 8)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 Sept. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 9)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 Oct. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 10)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 Nov. (Offsite-box 20, Folder 11)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1917 Dec. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 1)
    - Co. F: World War I Files--General Orders, 1917 Oct.-Dec. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 2)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1918 Jan.-Aug. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 3)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1918 Sept.-Oct. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 4)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1918 Nov. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 5)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1918 Dec. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 6)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1919 Jan. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 7)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1919 Feb. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 8)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, 1919 Mar.-Apr. (Offsite-box 21, Folder 9)
    - Co. F: World War I Files--Printed Material, 1919, undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 10)
    - Co. F: World War I Files, Undated (Offsite-box 21, Folder 11)
    - Co. F: Orders, 1822-1839, 1851, 1897 (Offsite-box 21, Folder 12)
    - Co. F: Morning Reports, 1918 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 1)
    - Co. F: Resolutions, Rosters, Passenger Lists, 1831-1919, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 2)
    - Co. F: Reports, 1945-1946 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 3)
    - Co. G: Enlistment Records, 1941-1948 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 4)
    - Co. G: Orders, 1822, 1844-1852, 1870, 1916 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 5)
    - Co. G: Resolutions, Minutes, 1857-1891 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 6)
    - Co. G: Rolls, Correspondence, 1827-1890 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 7)
    - Co. H: Orders, 1830-1834, 1853-1861 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 8)
    - Co. H: Resolutions, 1852-1892 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 9)
    - Co. H: Correspondence, Warrants, Reports, 1830-1854, 1906, 1949-1950 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 10)
    - Co. I: Manual, Training, Invites, 1866, 1878, 1909, undated (Offsite-box 22, Folder 11)
    - Co. K: Minutes, 1902-1909 (Offsite-box 22, Folder 12)
    - Co. K: Correspondence--Samuel Hoffman, Secretary, 1904-1909 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 1)
    - Co. K: Correspondence--Herbert Barnes, Secretary (Offsite-box 23, Folder 2)
    - Co. K: Resolutions, Correspondence, Financial, 1870-1955 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 3)
    - Co. K: Treasurer's Reports, 1901-1912 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 4)
    - Co. K: Booklets, 1940-1943 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 5)
    - Co. L: Reports, Memo, 1944, 1947 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 6)
    - Co. L: Newsletter ("The Lion"), 1937-1938, 1944 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 7)
    - Co. L: History, [1943] (Offsite-box 23, Folder 8)
    - Headquarters Co.: Enlistment Records, 1944-1949 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 9)
    - Band: Enlistment Records, 1941-1947 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 10)
    - Co. B, C, F, G, I, K: Newsletter, Undated (Offsite-box 23, Folder 11)
    - Medical Detachment: Enlistment Records, 1946-1948 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 12)
    - Company Orders: Unidentified Companies, 1818, 1822-1824, 1862 (Offsite-box 23, Folder 13)
  - Rolled Rosters:
    These rolled rosters are housed in a document box in the BV section.
    - Co. A, [1850s] (Volume BV)
    - Co. D, Undated (Volume BV)
    - Co. E, 1824 (Volume BV)
    - Co. F: Exempt Members, 1825-1828 (Volume BV)
    - Co. F, 1940 (Volume BV)
  - Bound Volumes:
    - Co. A: By-Laws, 1842 (Offsite-box SR-28, Volume 157)
    - Co. A: By-Laws, 1852 (Offsite-box SR-28, Volume 158)
    - Co. A: By-Laws, 1879 (Offsite-box SR-28, Volume 159)
    - Co. A: Membership Roll, 1806 (Offsite-box SR-28, Volume 160)
    - Co. A: Membership Roll, 1806 (Offsite-box SR-28, Volume 161)
    - Co. A: Rosters, 1877-1902 (Offsite-box SR-28, Volume 162)
    - Co. A: Roll Book, 1914 (Offsite-box SR-28, Volume 163)
    - Co. A: Minutes, 1846-1858 (Offsite-box SR-29, Volume 164)
    - Co. A: Minutes, 1858-1875 (Offsite-box SR-29, Volume 165)
    - Co. A: Court Martial Minutes, 1868-1884 (Offsite-box SR-29, Volume 166)
    - Co. A: Orders (oversize), 1882-1885 (Offsite-box SR-31, Volume 167)
    - Co. A: Daily Report, 1883 (Offsite-box SR-29, Volume 168)
    - Co. A: Cash Book, 1848-1879 (Offsite-box SR-29, Volume 169)
    - Co. A: Account Book, 1856-1859 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 170)
    - Co. A: Account Book, 1860-1862 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 171)
    - Co. A: Account Book, 1863-1864 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 172)
    - Co. A: Account Book, 1868-1871 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 173)
    - Co. A: Account Book--Monumental Fund, 1867-1873 (Offsite-box SR-29, Volume 174)
    - Co. A: Receipt Book, 1861-1893 (Offsite-box SR-29, Volume 175)
    - Co. A: Rifle Practice, 1882-1883 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 176)
    - Co. A: Rifle Practice, 1884-1885 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 177)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (in envelope), 1830, 1834, 1841, 1844, 1848 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 178)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (boxed), 1871, 1878, 1882 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 179)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1850 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 180)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1853 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 181)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1856 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 182)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1858 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 183)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1862 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 184)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1871 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 185)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (2 copies), 1878 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 186)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (2 copies), 1893 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 187)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (3 copies), 1897 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 188)
    - Co. B: By-Laws (3 copies), 1911 (Offsite-box SR-30, Volume 189)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1913 (Offsite-box SR-31, Volume 190)
    - Co. B: By-Laws, 1917 (Offsite-box SR-31, Volume 191)
    - Co. B: Rosters, 1858-1917 (Offsite-box SR-31, Volume 192)
    - Co. B: Member Roll, 1806-1825 (Offsite-box SR-31, Volume 193)
    - Co. B: Roll Book, 1843-1867 (Offsite-box SR-32, Volume 194)
    - Co. B: Roll Book, 1868-1889 (Offsite-box SR-32, Volume 195)
    - Co. B: Roll Book, 1889-1910 (Offsite-box SR-32, Volume 196)
    - Co. B: Roll Book, Honorary Members, 1859-1865 (Offsite-box SR-32, Volume 197)
    - Co. B: Register of Members, Ex-Members, Veterans, 1864-1910 (Offsite-box SR-32, Volume 198)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1826-1839 (Offsite-box SR-32, Volume 199)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1847-1852 (Offsite-box SR-32, Volume 200)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1852-1857 (Offsite-box SR-32, Volume 201)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1857-1862 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 202)
    - Co. B: Minute Book, 1914-1918 (Offsite-box SR-31, Volume 203)
    - Co. B: Record of Services, 1861-1863 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 204)
    - Co. B: Account Book, 1827-1838 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 205)
    - Co. B: Nonsense Rhymes, 1880 (Volume 206)
    - Co. B: Aqueduct Guard, 1917 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 207)
    - Co. C: By-Laws, 1846 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 208)
    - Co. C: By-Laws, 1860 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 209)
    - Co. C: By-Laws, 1876 (Volume 210)
    - Co. C: By-Laws (2), 1884 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 211)
    - Co. C: By-Laws, 1888 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 212)
    - Co. C: Rosters, 1887 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 213)
    - Co. C: Minute Book, 1847-1854 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 214)
    - Co. C: Roster (rolled, in metal tube), 1806 (Volume 215)
    - Co. D: By-Laws, 1823-1893 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 216)
    - Co. D: Roster (folded, in document box in BV), 1819-1846 (Volume 217)
    - Co. D: Roster (folded, in document box in BV), 1845-1871 (Volume 218)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1831-1840 (Offsite-box SR-33, Volume 219)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1841-1852 (Offsite-box SR-34, Volume 220)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1852-1859 (Offsite-box SR-34, Volume 221)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1860-1866 (Offsite-box SR-34, Volume 222)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1866-1875 (Offsite-box SR-34, Volume 223)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1875-1882 (Offsite-box SR-35, Volume 224)
    - Co. D: Record Book, 1882-1887 (Offsite-box SR-35, Volume 225)
    - Co. D: Minute Book, 1823-1831 (Offsite-box SR-35, Volume 226)
    - Co. D: Orderly Book, 1828-1839 (Offsite-box SR-35, Volume 227)
    - Co. D: Orderly Book, 1840-1859 (Offsite-box SR-37, Volume 228)
    - Co. D: Orders (oversize), 1873-1885 (Offsite-box SR-36, Volume 229)
    - Co. D: Account Book, 1817-1845 (Offsite-box SR-36, Volume 230)
    - Co. E: By-Laws, 1866 (Offsite-box SR-36, Volume 231)
    - Co. E: By-Laws, 1887 (Offsite-box SR-36, Volume 232)
    - Co. E: Roll Book, 1893 (Offsite-box SR-36, Volume 233)
    - Co. E: Roll Book, 1899 (Offsite-box SR-36, Volume 234)
    - Co. E: Secretary's Book, 1830-1847 (Offsite-box SR-38, Volume 235)
    - Co. E: Report Book, 1834-1844 (Offsite-box SR-38, Volume 236)
    - Co. E: Minute Book, 1848-1861 (Offsite-box SR-38, Volume 237)
    - Co. E: Minute Book, 1861-1876 (Offsite-box SR-37, Volume 238)
    - Co. E: Minute Book, 1876-1889 (Offsite-box SR-37, Volume 239)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1851-1859 (Offsite-box SR-38, Volume 240)
    - Co. E: Orders, 1872-1883 (Offsite-box SR-39, Volume 241)
    - Co. E: Account Book, 1834-1851 (Offsite-box SR-39, Volume 242)
    - Co. E: Returns (oversize), 1842-1859 (Offsite-box SR-40, Volume 243)
    - Co. E: Account Book--Returns of Delinquents, 1878-1891 (Offsite-box SR-40, Volume 244)
    - Co. F: By-Laws, 1834-1902 (Offsite-box SR-39, Volume 245)
    - Co. F: Rolls, Roster, Committees, 1874-1891 (Offsite-box SR-39, Volume 246)
    - Co. F: Roster (folded, in document box in BV), 1819-1900 (Volume 247)
    - Co. F: Roster (folded, in document box in BV), 1819-1940 (Volume 248)
    - Co. F: Roll Book, Undated (Offsite-box SR-39, Volume 249)
    - Co. F: Daily Report, 1883 (Offsite-box SR-40, Volume 250)
    - Co. F: Orderly Book, 1834-1847 (Offsite-box SR-41, Volume 251)
    - Co. F: Orders, 1836-1845 (Offsite-box SR-40, Volume 252)
    - Co. F: Orders, 1854-1863 (Offsite-box SR-40, Volume 253)
    - Co. F: Court Martial Returns (oversize), 1875-1893 (Offsite-box SR-42, Volume 254)
    - Co. F: Scrapbook, 1855-1866 (Offsite-box SR-43, Volume 255)
    - Co. F: Record Book--Rifle Practice, 1880-1885 (Offsite-box SR-43, Volume 256)
    - Co. G: By-Laws, 1833 (Offsite-box SR-41, Volume 257)
    - Co. G: By-Laws, 1861-1875 (Offsite-box SR-41, Volume 258)
    - Co. G: Rosters, 1888 (Offsite-box SR-41, Volume 259)
    - Co. G: Information Booklet, 1882 (Offsite-box SR-41, Volume 260)
    - Co. G: Monthly Report, 1868-1872 (Offsite-box SR-41, Volume 261)
    - Co. G: Minute Book, 1834-1852 (Offsite-box SR-41, Volume 262)
    - Co. G: Minute Book, 1852-1861 (Offsite-box SR-41, Volume 263)
    - Co. G: Minute Book, 1861-1876 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 264)
    - Co. G: Minute Book, 1876-1891 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 265)
    - Co. G: Orderly Book, 1865-1871 (Offsite-box SR-42, Volume 266)
    - Co. G: Orders, 1871-1881 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 267)
    - Co. G: Enlistment Roll (oversize), 1859-1914 (Offsite-box SR-43, Volume 268)
    - Co. H: By-Laws, 1829-1885 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 269)
    - Co. H: By-Laws, 1861 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 270)
    - Co. H: Roll Books, 1846-1890 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 271)
    - Co. H: Roll Book, 1876 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 272)
    - Co. H: Record Book, 1827-1829 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 273)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1827-1834 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 274)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1834-1835 (Offsite-box SR-44, Volume 275)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1835-1844 (Offsite-box SR-45, Volume 276)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1844-1855 (Offsite-box SR-45, Volume 277)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1855-1863 (Offsite-box SR-45, Volume 278)
    - Co. H: Minute Book, 1864-1875 (Offsite-box SR-45, Volume 279)
    - Co. I: By-Laws (in box), 1858, 1870, 1877, 1885 (Offsite-box SR-45, Volume 280)
    - Co. I: By-Laws (2 copies), 1870 (Offsite-box SR-45, Volume 281)
    - Co. I: By-Laws, 1877 (Offsite-box SR-45, Volume 282)
    - Co. I: Rosters, 1887-1922 (Offsite-box SR-46, Volume 283)
    - Co. I: Roster, 1838-1913 (Offsite-box SR-46, Volume 284)
    - Co. I: Roster, 1838-1938 (Offsite-box SR-46, Volume 285)
    - Co. I: Minutes, 1879-1891 (Offsite-box SR-46, Volume 286)
    - Co. I: Minutes, 1892-1908 (Offsite-box SR-46, Volume 287)
    - Co. I: Minutes, 1908-1917 (Offsite-box SR-46, Volume 288)
    - Co. I: Account Book, 1869-1872 (Offsite-box SR-47, Volume 289)
    - Co. I: Accounts Receivable, 1879-1880 (Offsite-box SR-45, Volume 290)
    - Co. I: Court Martial--Fines Levied, 1863-1865 (Offsite-box SR-47, Volume 291)
    - Co. I: Court Martial--Fines Levied, 1870-1872 (Offsite-box SR-47, Volume 292)
    - Co. I: Manual, 1935 (Offsite-box SR-47, Volume 293)
    - Co. I: 'Tin Soldiers', 1914 (Offsite-box SR-47, Volume 294)
    - Co. K: By-Laws, 1909 (Offsite-box SR-47, Volume 295)
    - Co. K: Rosters, 1877-1930 (Offsite-box SR-47, Volume 296)
    - Co. K: Minute Book, 1895-1906 (Offsite-box SR-47, Volume 297)
    - Co. K: Minute Book, 1906-1913 (Offsite-box SR-47, Volume 298)
    - Co. K: Memoranda, Undated (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 299)
    - Co. M: Roster and By-Laws, 1911 (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 300)
- Series III: Depot (Home) Battalion/Aqueduct Service, 1916-1929
  This series contains materials related to the Depot (Home) Battalion, 7th Infantry who defended the aqueduct in Pleasantville, New York during World War I in 1917. The materials summarize the duties of the men defending the aqueduct or relate to the Aqueduct Association, its veterans organization.
  - Roster, Depot Battalion, 7th Infantry, 1916 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 1)
  - "Greyjackets on the Aqueduct, 1917", 1922 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 2)
  - Aqueduct Association--Correspondence, 1927-1929 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 3)
  - Aqueduct Association--Materials re: Fifth and Sixth Annual Outings, 1924-1925 (Offsite-box 24, Folder 4)
  - Daily Report, 1917 Sept. (Offsite-box SR-48, Volume 301)
- Series IV: Francis D. Landon, 1908-1918
  Francis G. Landon (1859-1947) was a politician from New York City. He joined the 7th Regiment as a private, rose through the ranks and was promoted to Major. During the period ca.1912 to ca.1916, he was involved in the education of military officers, initially as a student, but later, apparently, as an instructor. Following the United States' declaration of war against Germany in 1917, Landon served as Morale Officer at Camp Merritt, NJ. This series consists of material that Landon accumulated primarily during these two stages of his career. The series is divided into three principal subseries. These are: General Correspondence, Military Education, and Camp Merritt, NJ.
  - Subseries 1: General Correspondence, 1909-1915
    The General Correspondence subseries consists of personal letters to Landon and his retained copies of his replies. Letters received by Landon are arranged chronologically in a folder titled General Correspondence - Letters Received. Landon's replies are arranged alphabetically, with one folder for each recipient of Landon's letters. The letters concern two subjects: the study of military history and a proposed program of rifle practice in colleges.
    - Letters Received, 1909, 1914-1915, undated (Offsite-box 25, Folder 1)
    - Major [ ] Hutchinson - Letters Received, 1915 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 2)
    - [ ] Parker - Letters Received, 1909 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 3)
    - Gen. [Chas. F.] Roe - Letters Received, 1909 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Military Education, 1912-1917
    Material in the Military Education subseries consists primarily of small booklets of problem-solving exercises for military officers. These booklets were published by the Army Service Schools, where Landon attended classes during the academic year 1913 - 1914, and perhaps at other times. For purposes of the arrangement of this series, these booklets are referred to as Map Problems, the genre name applied to most of the booklets. In those instances that Landon kept a map with the booklet, they are housed together. Otherwise, maps are housed separately. Also included in this subseries are Landon's solutions to some of the Map Problems, evidently composed as course work, and some problems that appear to have been composed by Landon, perhaps for courses that he taught. This material is arranged according to the particular school that issued it, or, if no specific school is identified, the course to which it pertains. If no school or course is specified, the folder title indicates only the type of material found within it.
    Landon appears to have taught at least one course in military tactics. Some material in the collection appears to be lecture notes or typewritten handouts that accompanied lectures. It some cases, it is unclear whether these notes and handouts are from lectures that Landon attended, or whether he composed them for lectures that he delivered. Some notes and typescripts pertaining to Landon's military education at Fort Leavenworth are identified as such.
    - Army School of the Line - Map Problems - Course in Tactics, 1912-1913 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 5)
    - Army School of the Line - Map Problems - Course in Tactics, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 6)
    - Army School of the Line - Map Problems - Course in Tactics, 1914-1915 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 7)
    - Army School of the Line - Map Problems - Course in Tactics, 1915-1916 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 8)
    - Army School of the Line - [Map Problems] - Terrain Exercise #6, 1913 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 9)
    - Army School of the Line - [Map Problems] - The Rifle in War, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 10)
    - Army School of the Line - Organization of the German Army, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 11)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - Map Problems, 1912 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 12)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - Map Problems, 1913 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 13)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - Map Problems, 1914 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 14)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - List of Lessons & Exercises, 1914 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 15)
    - Special Course for the Instruction of Field Officers - Topics for Discussion, 1914 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 16)
    - Special Class for Field Officers - Tactical Ride, 1914 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 17)
    - Special Class for Field Officers - Map Maneuvers, 1912-1914 (Offsite-box 25, Folder 18)
    - Army Field Engineers' School - Course List, 1913-1914 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 1)
    - Army Field Engineers' School - Quiz, 1914 Jan. (Offsite-box 26, Folder 2)
    - Provisional Officers' Class - Map Problems, 1917 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 3)
    - [Provisional Officers' Class] - Musketry Problems, 1917, undated (Offsite-box 26, Folder 4)
    - Army Staff College - Course in Historical Research, [1912-1913] (Offsite-box 26, Folder 5)
    - Army Service Schools - Map Problems - Solutions Submitted by Landon (1 of 2), 1914 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 6)
    - Army Service Schools - Map Problems - Solutions Submitted by Landon (2 of 2), 1914 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 7)
    - Army Service Schools - Map Problems - Tables of Troop Blocks for Maps, 1914 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 8)
    - Army Service Schools - Memoranda, 1914 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 9)
    - Army Service Schools - Reprint of Order - 9th U.S. Inf., 1914 (Offsite-box 26, Folder 10)